

## Ferhat Adıbelli

• Address: Gazeteci Hasan Tahsin Cad., No:77, Karabağlar, 35150, İzmir, Turkey

Email address: ferhatadibelli9@gmail.com Phone number: (+90) 5459433435

**Website:** <a href="https://ferhatadibelli0.github.io/Portfolio/">https://ferhatadibelli0.github.io/Portfolio/</a>

in LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ferhat-adibelli-330b27235/

Stackoverflow: <a href="https://stackoverflow.com/users/19093788/ferhat-adibelli">https://stackoverflow.com/users/19093788/ferhat-adibelli</a>

Github: <a href="https://github.com/FerhatAdibelli0">https://github.com/FerhatAdibelli0</a>

**Gender:** Male **Date of birth:** 15/11/1991 **Nationality:** Turkish

### **ABOUT ME**

I'm Ferhat. I am from Turkey, I live in Turkey. As a FullStack Developer, I`m very passionate and talented about **ReactJS**, **NextJS**, **NodeJS**, **ExpressJS**, **MongoDB**, **and MySQL**. I devoted myself to learning, implementing, adapting, and creating throughout my life to build intelligent web apps to help people and improve life quality around the world. As a Web Developer with 14 months of experience able to build web applications from the ground up - information gathering, planning, design, development, testing and delivery, and maintenance.

### **DIGITAL SKILLS**

Very good at programming in: HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Boostrap, Jquery, Javascript | React ecosystem: ReactJS, React Router, Redux, Typescript | Backend: NodeJS, Express, socket.io | RESTful api | Git | Github | graphQL | DenoJs | nextjs | Agile (Scrum) | Postman | FireBase | Basic knowledge of JIRA | Heroku Cloud | Web Socket | Unit Testing | API Integrations | Sequelize and Mongoose | Object-Oriented Programming | MongoDB, MySQL

# EDUCATION AND TRAINING

[2010 - 2014] Bachelor of Science

Turkish Military Academy - Ankara

Field(s) of study: Industrial and Systems Engineering

Final grade: 3.65/4

[ 2020 - Current ] Master's degree (Thesis)

Gazi Univercity - Ankara

Field(s) of study: Computer Forensic

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## [ 02/2022 - 05/2022 ] **Frontend Developer**

Alme Tech

**Country:** Turkey

Main activities and responsibilities:

Building user interfaces for websites and/or web applications Working with ReactJS, Redux, TypeScript Creating self-contained, reusable, and testable modules and components Writing some end-to-end test on JestJS

[ 10/2021 - 01/2022 ] Freelancer

Upwork

**Country:** Turkey

Main activities and responsibilities:

Upwork helped me find my first job as a Frontend Developer.. It allows me to focus on what is most important for my clients - product and project development.

### **HONOURS AND AWARDS**

React|S -- The Complete Guide Awarding institution: Academind https://drive.google.com/file/d/1UPC\_WHLoWUOf9ADO-6JEahHS7nlzeJb0/view? usp=sharing

React|S -- Web Programming Awarding institution: BTK Academy https://drive.google.com/file/d/1GlUX8brBrknCW8iVHf1Wg CLPz g7vMr/view? usp=sharing

Node|S -- The Complete Guide Awarding institution: Academind https://drive.google.com/file/d/1QxMxt8Wh-j9NF83Sqqsbr8l3E6rRcaqK/view?usp=sharing

Git & Github -- Version Control System Awarding institution: BTK Academy https://drive.google.com/file/d/17g fC7fDGiHUKurpCb3R6 6AxzE91zq4/view?usp=sharing

Language Competency Awarding institution: American Culture School https://drive.google.com/file/d/1HOzdEH-8ytlH\_u9XtqXbyaSJIGwNmwDa/view? usp=sharing